animenation.com 2001-12-04

# AnimeNation - The Anime Source for videos, books, games and other anime merchandise ! Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

AnimeNation has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment your privacy. We do not sell or share your personal information or email address with any third party. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites: [http://www.animenation.com](http://www.animenation.com/) and [http://www.animenation.net](http://www.animenation.net/).

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. AnimeNation is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). This information is only used to contact visitors regarding that contest. The information is not used any time for any other purpose. 

Any personal information (email address, home address etc) we obtain from visitors/customers will not be sold or shared with any third party. All information gathered is used for internal purposes only. 

Choice/Opt-Out

To be removed from our email list please email [list@AnimeNation.com](mailto:list@animenation.com) . If you are using a email forwarding service or other similar service please make sure to include the correct email address or addresses.

To be removed from our catalog and update mailing list please email [sales@AnimeNation.com](mailto:sales@animenation.org). Be sure to include your name or name used on any orders placed and your mailing address. 

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  
Webmaster  
AnimeNation  
13929 Lynmar Blvd.  
Tampa FL 33626
